Ganzorig Erdenebat

Address: Miami, FL https://rozig.github.io Mobile: +1 (312) 404-1266

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/rozig/ Email: the.ganzorig25@gmail.com

Summary

Accomplished full-stack engineer with over 3 years of experience playing key role in system design, development, deployment and support of enterprise-level software. Strong technical skills, with hands-on experience with several popular web frameworks including Django, Flask, NodeJS and Angular. Personable team player with talent for collaborating with diverse technical teams. Skills developing REST APIs and integrating with third party APIs. Strong SQL and ORM skills, experience with PostgreSQL, Doctrine and SQLAlchemy. Expertise with Linux use and administration, experience with Docker and AWS.

EDUCATION

Maharishi University of Management

Master of Science in Computer Science; GPA: 3.90

Oct. 2017 - Present

Fairfield, IA

Mongolian University of Science and Technology

Bachelor of Science in Software Engineering; GPA: 3.46

Ulaanbaatar, Mongolia Aug. 2013 - Jan. 2017

EXPERIENCE

Genius Plaza Inc.

Full-stack Developer

Miami, FL

Aug. 2018 - Present

- Genius Plaza: RESTful API development on Django and DjangoREST Framework.
- Genius Baby: Works on microservices, RESTful API, web application development and deployment.

Infinite Solutions LLC

Full-stack Developer

Ulaanbaatar, Mongolia Jun. 2016 - Nov. 2017

- o Transfer: Transfer is a fintech solution for receiving and sending money over the world. Worked on core system, API services and front-end development.
- Mobicom Branded Application: Managed back-end server for Mobicom Branded Application. Performed backend development, API services development, testing and maintenance and database design.
- o Golds Gym Website: Developed official website for Golds Gym Mongolia. Conducted unit testing and maintenance. Performed front-end and back-end development.
- ArigBank: In-charge of maintenance and front-end development.

Projects

- React.js boilerplate: Boilerplate project for React.js. Used webpack, styled-components and react-router.
- Online Publication Platform: Clone of Medium.com, built RESTful API and implemented JWT authentication.
- Mumagram: Instagram-like social networking web application for MUM students.
- MUMSched: Academic scheduling web application for MUM students.
- Online Banking Application: Web application that allows user to transfer money and manage their accounts.
- Nutrition Calculator: Nutrition calculator web application on Django (Python).
- Logistics System: Web application for cargo delivery on Diango (Python).

PROGRAMMING SKILLS

SDLC: Agile/SCRUM, RUP, Waterfall • Languages: Python, PHP, JavaScript, TypeScript, Bash, SQL

• Web/App Servers: Nginx, Apache2, Node Frameworks: Diango, Flask, Symfony, NodeJS, Angular

• Web: jQuery, CSS3/HTML5, SASS, Express, React, Webpack, Redux Platforms: UNIX/Linux, Windows

• Design Patterns: Factory Method, Singleton, MVC Web Services: REST, DjangoREST, GraphQL

• Tools: Git, Vim, Terminal, AWS, GCP, Bash, zsh Databases: MySQL, PostgreSQL, SQLAlchemy